<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
        <string name="botonhomehoteles">Hotels</string>
        <string name="botonhomerestaurantes">Restaurants</string>
        <string name="botonsitioshome">Tourist Sites</string>
        <string name="app_name">ElCarmen</string>
        <string name="titulohomehoteles">Hotels in El Carmen de Viboral</string>
        <string name="descripcionhomehoteles">Hotels in El Carmen de Viboral, Antioquia: Natural charm, modern comfort. Discover the beauty of the region in cozy accommodations.</string>
        <string name="titulohomerestaurantes">Restaurants in El Carmen de Viboral</string>
        <string name="descripcionhomerestaurantes">Intense flavors, arepas, bandeja paisa, and sweet desserts. Culinary tradition celebrating the richness of Antioquia in every bite.</string>
        <string name="titulohomesitios">Tourist Sites</string>
        <string name="menuopcion1">English</string>
        <string name="menuopcion2">Spanish</string>
        <string name="menuopcion3">Italian</string>
        <string name="menuopcion4">Review</string>
        <string name="menuopcion5">About</string>
        <string name="Botonhomesitios">See more sites</string>
        <string name="descripcionhomesitios">El Carmen de Viboral, Antioquia: Majestic waterfalls, mystical caves, and lush nature. Discover the magic of this Colombian destination.</string>
        <string name="ResenaCarmen">
        El Carmen de Viboral, Antioquia, captivates with its natural beauty: breathtaking waterfalls, crystal-clear rivers, and mountainous landscapes. This Colombian destination offers a unique experience, blending rural serenity with exciting outdoor activities. Explore the rich local culture and enjoy hospitality in this charming corner.
    </string>
        <string name="tituloresena">Review of El Carmen de Viboral</string>
        <string name="tituloacercade">Diomer Alexander Rua Rua</string>
        <string name="AcercadeDescripcion">Diomer Alexander Rua Rua stands out for his 28 years of age and solid training in software development, including prior technology experience at SENA. He exhibits exceptional mastery of programming logic, teamwork skills, and punctuality. His experience and skills make him a valuable asset to any software development team.</string>
</resources>